[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "No  triangle is car, all  figures are  triangles",
    "answerIndex": 0,
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "No car is  figure",
      "All cars are  figures",
      "Some cars are  figures",
      "Some cars are not  figures"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "All squares are  rectangles, no  rectangle is  square",
    "answerIndex": 1,
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "All squares are  squares",
      "No square is  square",
      "Some squares are  squares",
      "Some squares are not  squares"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "All equilaterals are  squares, no  rectangle is  square",
    "answerIndex": "No equilateral is  rectangle",
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "All equilaterals are  rectangles",
      "Some equilaterals are  rectangles",
      "Some equilaterals are not  rectangles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "All squares are  rectangles, no  rectangle is  circle",
    "answerIndex": 3,
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "All squares are  circles",
      "Some squares are  circles",
      "Some squares are not  circles",
      "No square is  circle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "All equilaterals are  squares, all  squares are  rectangles",
    "answerIndex": 2,
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "All equilaterals are  rectangles",
      "No equilateral is  rectangle",
      "Some equilaterals are  rectangles",
      "Some equilaterals are not  rectangles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "All rectangles are  squares, no  triangle is  square",
    "answerIndex": 1,
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "All rectangles are  triangles",
      "No rectangle is  triangle",
      "Some rectangles are  triangles",
      "Some rectangles are not  triangles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "No  square is bear, all  rectangles are  squares",
    "answerIndex": 2,
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "All bears are  rectangles",
      "Some bears are  rectangles",
      "No bear is  rectangle",
      "Some bears are not  rectangles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "No mammal is  dog, all  mammals are  dogs",
    "answerIndex": 3,
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "All mammals are  mammals",
      "Some mammals are  mammals",
      "Some mammals are not  mammals",
      "No mammal is  mammal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "All squares are  rectangles, all  rectangles are  squares",
    "answerIndex": 0,
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "Some squares are  squares",
      "All squares are  squares",
      "No square is  square",
      "Some squares are not  squares"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "All employees are  mammals, no  mammal is  plant",
    "answerIndex": 2,
    "wrongAnswers": [
      "All employees are  plants",
      "Some employees are  plants",
      "No employee is  plant",
      "Some employees are not  plants"
    ]
  }
]
